asiame.com 2018-08-06

# Privacy Policy - See How to Protect Yourself When Dating Asian Girls on Asiame.com.

Welcome to AsiaMe.com ("AsiaMe" or the "Site"). We understand that the privacy of our members, subscribers, guests and/or visitors ("Members", "you" or "your") is very important. As such, we provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal data is collected, processed, maintained and disposed by AsiaMe, a subsidiary site of Qpid Network. The [Privacy Policy](https://secure.qpidnetwork.com/help/privacy.php) describes how we treat your Personal Information when you use AsiaMe.com, as part of Qpid Network services ("Services"). The following describes our privacy practices that are specific to AsiaMe.com and other Qpid Network sites. We reserve the right to update it at any time, and all changes are effective upon posting without notice to you. You are encouraged to revisit this page from time to time. Your use of the Site or our Services after such changes constitutes your agreement to such changes.

* ### What Information We Collect

The types of Personal Information that we collect fall under two general categories: personally identifiable information (PII) and non-personally identifiable information (non-PII). PII consists of any information which can be used to specifically identify you as an individual, whereas non-PII consists of aggregate information or any information that does not reveal your identity. The following paragraphs explain what PII and non-PII we collect from you, and how we use such information.

* ### How We Collect and Use Information

  * _Cookies._  We use "cookies" to keep track of some types of information while you are visiting any of our Websites or using our services. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to our websites and distinguish repeat visitors from new ones. They also allow us to save member preferences and track member trends. We rely on cookies for the proper operation of our Websites; therefore if your browser is set to reject all cookies, the Website(s) will not function properly and you may not enjoy all of our Services. Members who refuse cookies assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality of our Websites. We do not link the cookies to any of our members’ PII.

  * _Log Files._  Any time you visit any of our Websites, our servers automatically gather information from your browser (such as your IP addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks) to analyze trends, administer our Websites, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad visitor demographic information. For example, we may log your IP address for system administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user’s session. This gives us an idea of which parts of our Websites our members are visiting. We do not share the log files externally.

  * _Web Beacons._  "Web beacons" (also known as "clear gifs" and "pixel tags") are small transparent graphic images that are often used in conjunction with cookies in order to further personalize our Websites for our users and to collect a limited set of information about our visitors. We may also use web beacons in email communications sent to you in order to understand the behavior of our members. We do not link the web beacons to any of our members’ PII.

  * _Mobile Analytics._ We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use our applications, the events that occur within the applications, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any of your submitted PII within the mobile application.

  * _Your Information._  When you register or subscribe to any of our Services, we collect a wide variety of information about you. Your profile information, including non-PII about yourself (such as first name, nationality, profession, height, weight, etc.) will be used to build your "My Profile." We may also display your relationship status and other profile/account information to your matches. Finally, for interactive content, including but not limited to CharmLive, where you may choose to have a public profile, we may display your information to other members and visitors. You may choose to provide us with your photo(s) or video(s) and by providing us such content, you agree that we may make them available to your matches and users of our Services. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose your PII to your matches or other users of our Services.

  * _Purchase Information._  To process purchases, we may require your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information. Such information is used primarily to process your order or as otherwise described herein. Credit card transactions are processed through industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and/or strong encryption (3DES) by a third party, which only uses your information for that purpose.

  * _E-mails._  You are require to produce an e-mail address when you register for our Services. We use your e-mail for both transactional (e.g. order placement and confirmation, refund and renewal processing, notifying you of our suggested matches) and promotional (e.g., newsletters, new product offerings, special discounts, event notifications, special third-party offers) purposes. Our e-mail messages may contain codes that enable our database to track your usage of the e-mails, including whether the e-mail was opened and what links (if any) were opened. If you do not want to receive promotional e-mails from us, please see the section below labeled "Opt-Out". We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our Services, such as service announcements, terms and policies updates and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. We may also contact you by email, tickets and/or telephone (including to any wireless number you may provide to us) solely in connection with our Services. If you would rather not receive emails, tickets or telephone calls from us, you may change or delete your number by contacting us for it to be removed from our contact list. 

  * _Mobile Device_  If you use your mobile device to access our Websites or download any of our applications, we may collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer), operating system information, IP address and etc. We collect your geolocation information only with your consent.

  * _Demographic Data._  We collect demographic data from our members and visitors. We use this data to tailor your user experience at our Websites, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences. Some of this information may be shared with advertisers on a non-personally identifiable basis.

  * _Online Survey Data._  We may periodically conduct voluntary member surveys. We encourage you to participate in such surveys to help us improve our Services. All responses are anonymous and do not involve any of your PII. 

* ### Mobile Device Additional Terms

  * _Mobile Device_  If you use a mobile device to access our site or download any of our applications, we may collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer), operating system and version information, and IP address. 

  * _Geo-Location Information._  We do not ask you for, access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile apps or our Services.

  * _Push Notifications._  We send you push notifications if you choose to receive them for notifying you of our matching services, letting you know when someone has sent you a message, or for other related matters. If you wish to opt-out from receiving these types of communications you may turn them off at the device level.

* ### Disclosure of Your Information

  * _Disclosure to Your Matches._  Our matching services remain an integral part of providing our Services which involves disclosing your profile information to your matches. Photos and other profile information posted by you will be available to other members matched with you. We never share your contact information with your matches without your consent.

  * _Disclosure By Law._  You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to (1) comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is required by applicable law); (2) protect or defend our company’s rights, or a third party’s, rights or property; or (3) protect someone’s health or safety, such as when harm or violence against any person (including you) is threatened.

  * _Disclosure to Protect Abuse Victims._  Notwithstanding any other provision of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use we reserve the right, but have no obligation, to disclose any information that you submit to the services, if in our sole opinion, we suspect or have reason to suspect, that the information involves a party who may be the victim of abuse in any form. Abuse may include, without limitation, bullying, elder abuse, child abuse, spousal abuse, neglect, or domestic violence. Information may be disclosed to authorities that we, in our sole discretion, deem appropriate to handle such disclosure. Appropriate authorities may include, without limitation, law enforcement agencies, child protection agencies, or court officials. You hereby acknowledge and agree that we are permitted to make such disclosure.

  * _Disclosure to Trusted Third Parties By Us._  We may share your non-PII with our third parties, but not in a manner that would reveal your personal identity. We may share your PII, sometimes in conjunction with your non-PII, with service providers that may be associated with us to perform functions on our behalf. For example, outsourced translation agents or IT technology contractors may need access to your information to perform services for you. Your information will be treated as private and confidential by such service providers and will not used for any purpose other than those identified in the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

  * _Information Transferred As a Result of Sale of Business._  As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets and, depending on the transaction, your PII may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that we are acquired by another company, your PII may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. If this occurs, you will be notified if there are any material changes to the way your PII is collected or used.

* ### Third-Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising agencies or other service providers to serve ads on our website on behalf of Asiame.com or third-party advertisers (e.g., retailers of goods or services). These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is completely anonymous.

* ### Age Restrictions

Our age restrictions are set forth in each applicable Terms of Use. We do not target our Websites or our Services to anyone under the age of 18, any information we may receive from any visitor we believe to be under the age of 18 will be deleted from our database.

* ### Security

We use encryption and authentication tools to guard against loss, misuse and alteration of our your information shared with us. Security measures include the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and/or strong encryption (3DES) technology during credit card transactions and administrative access to site data, which are applied to all repositories and transfers of user information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will do our best to protect its security on our systems.

* ### Links to or Access from Other Sites

You may be able to access your account or content of your account from third party sites, such as social networking sites, by way of various applications. The privacy policies and practices of such sites which apply to information you provided to such sites may differ from our practices as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to review their policies and practices to ensure that your privacy is protected. Such sites may also place their cookies or other files on your computer and they may collect personal data or solicit other information from you. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any Personal Information on such site.

* ### Opt-Out

You may use the following options for removing your information, including any unauthorized profile, from our e-mail database if you wish to opt out of receiving promotional e-mails and newsletters.  
1.Click on the "unsubscribe" link on the bottom of the e-mail;  
2.Send ticket to us letting us know which promotional e-mails you wish to opt-out of; or  
3.Select from our FAQs to find the answer you are looking for, or send us a ticket and our customer service team will be happy to assist you.

* ### Updating Your Personal Information

We provide users the following options for updating information previously submitted, including deletion of your Personal Information.  
1.For account settings, you may change your personal information such as height, weight, ethnicity and other information from "My Profile" settings; or  
2.You can send ticket to our customer service team to amend or delete your account information at any time. 

* ### Data Retention

Because many of our members tend to use our Services at different points of their relationship-seeking life, we retain your Personal Information for continued service and convenience purposes until you advise us not to do so. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may retain Personal Information in order to comply with applicable laws, keep accurate records, resolve disputes, prevent fraud, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or for any other legally permissible purpose.

* ### Information Protection

  * _Your Data Protection._ We take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your data on our Platform. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of our Platform, website, member database and records, no application, website or Internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe and to log out of your Account after use.

  * _Your Account and Password(s)._ You should not disclose or share your login details to any third parties. Try not to use your birthdate or anything too obvious or predictable as your password(s) such that unscruplous individuals may try to gain unauthorized access to your Account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password(s) and for restricting access to your computer, and for all activities that occur under your Account or password(s). We will not be liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your Account or password(s), either with or without your knowledge. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your Account and/or password(s) and any other breach of security relating to our Platform and websites. You agree that any information you provide to us will be current, accurate and complete and that you will keep such information up to date by notifying us of any changes.

* ### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Websites, or your dealings with any of our Websites, you can contact us at 

* ### Onward transfer and consent to international processing

We are a growing corporation with users and operations in multiple countries, including the European Union. We have developed data practices designed to assure information is appropriately protected but we cannot always know where Personal Information may be accessed or processed. In addition, we may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. If we disclose Personal Information to such authorised third party, we will seek assurances that any information we may provide to them is safeguarded adequately and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the requirements of applicable privacy laws.

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your personal data, including sensitive data, by us from your region to countries which do not have data protection laws that provide the same level of protection that exists in countries in the European Economic Area. By providing your Personal Information, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

* ### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your use of our Websites, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the applicable Terms of Use.  **BY USING OUR WEBSITES, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE TERMS OF USE.**

If we decide to amend our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page and additionally any other place on the Websites we deem appropriate so that you may become aware of it. We reserve our right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please come and revisit this page frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, or by other means, such as e-mail, at our discretion.

Your continued use of any portion of our Websites following posting of our updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

* ### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last revised on May 24, 2018.  
Copyright © 1998-2018 Asia Maritus Limited. All Rights Reserved. Other trademarks and brands are the property of their respective owners.
